<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Thomas M. Porter II</title>
    <link>https://thomasmporter.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Thomas M. Porter II</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2019 06:26:52 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://thomasmporter.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to install Encarta 96... on Windows 95... on DOSBox</title>
      <link>https://thomasmporter.github.io/post/encarta-on-dosbox/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2019 06:26:52 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thomasmporter.github.io/post/encarta-on-dosbox/</guid>
      <description>The song Still Alive in the Classic Valve game Portal has the lyric:
 &amp;ldquo;We do what we must, because we can&amp;rdquo;
 I can&amp;rsquo;t think of a better way to describe what I&amp;rsquo;m about to present.
Nobody needs to run Encarta 96 in a virtualized Windows 95 environment, unless there is a very particular need to feel nostalgic for mid-1990s computing.
So Then, Why Exactly? It started with a Tweet by @shanselman that got people taking about pre-internet Wikipedia, otherwise known as Microsoft Encarta:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who Put the Sec in DevSecOps</title>
      <link>https://thomasmporter.github.io/post/who-put-the-sec/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2019 17:07:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thomasmporter.github.io/post/who-put-the-sec/</guid>
      <description>A video about DevSecOps by yours truly!
  My second video is up: “Who Put the Sec in DevSecOps” - the origin and use of the buzzword “DevSecOps” https://t.co/vjaQdIbBky #Buzzwords #DevSecOps
&amp;mdash; Tom Porter “as Code” (@ThomasMPorterII) August 4, 2019  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Buzzword Economy</title>
      <link>https://thomasmporter.github.io/post/the-buzzword-economy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2019 17:07:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thomasmporter.github.io/post/the-buzzword-economy/</guid>
      <description>A video about Buzzwords by yours truly!
  I recorded the shorter version of one of the presentations I’ve pitched for a few calls for papers (it hasn’t been accepted yet 🙁). It’s not much, but hopefully the start of something: The Buzzword Economy https://t.co/p0hu6hW01g
&amp;mdash; Tom Porter “as Code” (@ThomasMPorterII) July 30, 2019  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finally</title>
      <link>https://thomasmporter.github.io/post/finally/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 18:26:52 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thomasmporter.github.io/post/finally/</guid>
      <description>It took a hot minute, but I finally got an Azure Pipeline to deploy my hugo source to GitHub Pages.
It isn&amp;rsquo;t pretty, and I&amp;rsquo;d like to write something without using pieced together marketplace tasks (if possible), but I&amp;rsquo;ll take what I can get for now!
I hope I can use this as a way to test out and share knowledge.
Here&amp;rsquo;s Hoping..</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vs Launch Az</title>
      <link>https://thomasmporter.github.io/post/vs-launch-az/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 16:34:14 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thomasmporter.github.io/post/vs-launch-az/</guid>
      <description>Here are my sketch notes from the #VSLaunchAZ event I attended today.
Lots of great info on new stuff to tide me over until //build.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I Stuck With Roku After Trying FireTV</title>
      <link>https://thomasmporter.github.io/post/why-i-stuck-with-roku-after-trying-firetv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2017 19:46:17 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thomasmporter.github.io/post/why-i-stuck-with-roku-after-trying-firetv/</guid>
      <description>TL;DR: Amazon FireTV is a great platform, but it does not have an (official) application to access our UltraViolet Library. Too much focus on Amazon content and Ads.
Our household has been using Roku devices exclusively for many years. We recently we got the opportunity to see what it’s like to use an Amazon FireTV 2. I was curiously to see what we’ve been missing.
As a background, we use quite a few services: Netflix, Hulu, Amazon Prime, Vudu, HBO Now, Starz, PlayStation Vue, and YouTubeRed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Beginning</title>
      <link>https://thomasmporter.github.io/post/the-beginning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2016 18:36:04 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thomasmporter.github.io/post/the-beginning/</guid>
      <description>So, I’ve been a Microsoft .NET programmer for over ten years.
Ten years.
In this decade of coding professionally:
 I haven’t blogged about programming. I’ve barely tweeted about it. I haven’t contributed to one open source project. I haven’t answered one forum post or Stack Overflow question. I haven’t attended a local .NET user group.  I’m not bragging. Looking back, I wish I had done more outside of work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://thomasmporter.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thomasmporter.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description> Your Name Email Address An email address is required.  Message   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>